scottbuehler.com 2018-01-03

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: February 5th, 2014

This privacy statement describes how ScottBuehler.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [www.scottbuehler.com](http://www.scottbuehler.com/ "Scott Buehler") . It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact us on our [contact form](http://www.scottbuehler.com/contact-scott/ "Contact Scott"). Should that form not function properly, please contact via email using privacy -at- thissitesdomain.com

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register an account on ScottBuehler.com, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When signing up to our newsletters, sending us an email, or registering an account on ScottBuehler.com, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your full name and valid email address. You may, however, visit ScottBuehler.com anonymously by not participating with our newsletters, contact forms, and by not registering an account here.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy page.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience**  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * **To improve our website**  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * **To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * **To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature**
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide when singing up for our company newsletters will be used to send you information about updates to our website, current offers, and will include advertisements we think may interest you.

## Unsubscribe Policy

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or notification.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Information submitted from our [contact form](http://www.scottbuehler.com/contact-scott/ "Contact Scott") is not stored in a database and is immediately deleted from our servers after the email is delivered.

Our newsletter subscriptions are handled via a third party company and this information is not stored on our website. ScottBuehler.com shall not be held liable for security related issues from our third party newsletter company since we have no control over their data.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. ScottBuehler.com uses cookies.

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party partners

ScottBuehler.com has teamed up with reputable third party vendors in order to provide certain services to its online users. When leaving our website to view one of our partner websites, we encourage users to review the privacy statements of those websites as we cannot guarantee the privacy of users while visiting affiliate sites.

ScottBuehler.com may use third-party companies to serve ads or analyze behavior patterns when you visit our Web site. These companies may place or provide ads (such as banner ads) on this Web site that might also place cookies. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our Web site in order to help us improve our user experience and/or provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of providing these services or placing these ads, these third-party companies may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your computer and each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. Our Website may also use Web beacons in conjunction with cookies. Web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a Web page, (sometimes referred to as “1×1 clear pixel,” “Web beacon” or “clear GIF”) in the pages of our Web site in order to gather additional statistical site usage information.

If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. Be advised that if you change computers or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through ScottBuehler.com and not to information collected offline.

## Limitation of Liability

SCOTTBUEHLER.COM SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE IN ANY MANNER FOR THE ACTS OF ANY THIRD PARTY, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY THIRD PARTY AD NETWORK.

## Your Consent

By using the ScottBuehler.com website, you signify your acceptance of this website privacy policy.  If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use ScottBuehler.com. Your continued use of any Buehlerfam Creations, Inc. site following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

**This policy was last modified on February 5th, 2014.**

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Buehlerfam Creations, Inc.  
PO BOX 2642  
Cedar City, Utah 84721  
United States  
You may also email as using [this email form](http://www.scottbuehler.com/contact-scott/ "Contact Scott").
